// export const jsQuestions = [
//     {"qNo": "01_", "question": "222222Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooons ?", "answers": "de Boulogne", "correct": '1'},
//         {"qNo": "02_", "question": "11111Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooon ?", "answers": "Apollo 7", "correct": '1'},
//         {"qNo": "03_", "question": "333333Who starred in the 1959 epic film Ben Hur ?", "answers": "Charlton Heston", "correct": '1'},
//         {"qNo": "04_", "question": "444444Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooon?", "answers": "de Boulogne", "correct": '3'},
//         {"qNo": "05_", "question": "55555555Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooon ?", "answers": "Apollo 7", "correct": '1'},
//         {"qNo": "06_", "question": "6666666Who starred in the 1959 epic film Ben Hur ?", "answers": "Charlton Heston", "correct": '2'},
//         {"qNo": "07_", "question": "777777The Eiffel Tower is located where in Paris  where in Paris?", "answers": "de Boulogne", "correct": '1'},
//         {"qNo": "08_", "question": "88888888Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooon ?", "answers": "Apollo 7", "correct": '1'},
//         {"qNo": "09_", "question": "9999999Who starred in the 1959 epic film Ben Hur ?", "answers": "Charlton Heston", "correct": '2'},
//         {"qNo": "10_", "question": "1000The Eiffel Tower is located where in Paris ?", "answers": "de Boulogne", "correct": '3'},
//         {"qNo": "12_", "question": "11111Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooon ?", "answers": "Apollo 7", "correct": '1'},
//         {"qNo": "13_", "question": "1222222222222Who starred in the 1959 epic film Ben Hur where in Paris?", "answers": "Charlton Heston", "correct": '2'},
//         {"qNo": "14_", "question": "133333333333The Eiffel Tower is located where in Paris where in Paris?", "answers": "de Boulogne", "correct": '1'}
// ];

export const jsQuestions = [
    {
        qNo: '01_',
        question:
            '222222Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooons ?',
        answers: [
            'de Boulogne',
            'Champ de Mars',
            'Jardin des Plantes',
            'Parc de Belleville'
        ],
        correct: '1'
    },
    {
        qNo: '02_',
        question:
            '11111Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooon ?',
        answers: ['Apollo 7', 'Apollo 9', 'Apollo 11', 'Apollo 13'],
        correct: '1'
    },
    {
        qNo: '03_',
        question: '333333Who starred in the 1959 epic film Ben Hur ?',
        answers: [
            'Charlton Heston',
            'Clark Gable',
            'Errol Flynn',
            'Lee Marvin'
        ],
        correct: '1'
    },
    {
        qNo: '04_',
        question:
            '444444Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooon?',
        answers: [
            'de Boulogne',
            'Bios de Boulogne',
            'Bios de Boulogne',
            'Bios de Boulogne'
        ],
        correct: '3'
    },
    {
        qNo: '05_',
        question:
            '55555555Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooon ?',
        answers: ['Apollo 7', 'Apollo 9', 'Apollo 11', 'Apollo 13'],
        correct: '1'
    },
    {
        qNo: '06_',
        question: '6666666Who starred in the 1959 epic film Ben Hur ?',
        answers: [
            'Charlton Heston',
            'Clark Gable',
            'Errol Flynn',
            'Lee Marvin'
        ],
        correct: '2'
    },
    {
        qNo: '07_',
        question:
            '777777The Eiffel Tower is located where in Paris  where in Paris?',
        answers: [
            'de Boulogne',
            'Champ de Mars',
            'Jardin des Plantes',
            'Parc de Belleville'
        ],
        correct: '1'
    },
    {
        qNo: '08_',
        question:
            '88888888Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooon ?',
        answers: ['Apollo 7', 'Apollo 9', 'Apollo 11', 'Apollo 13'],
        correct: '1'
    },
    {
        qNo: '09_',
        question: '9999999Who starred in the 1959 epic film Ben Hur ?',
        answers: [
            'Charlton Heston',
            'Clark Gable',
            'Errol Flynn',
            'Lee Marvin'
        ],
        correct: '2'
    },
    {
        qNo: '10_',
        question: '1000The Eiffel Tower is located where in Paris ?',
        answers: [
            'de Boulogne',
            'Bios de Boulogne',
            'Bios de Boulogne',
            'Bios de Boulogne'
        ],
        correct: '3'
    },
    {
        qNo: '12_',
        question:
            '11111Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooon ?',
        answers: ['Apollo 7', 'Apollo 9', 'Apollo 11', 'Apollo 13'],
        correct: '1'
    },
    {
        qNo: '13_',
        question:
            '1222222222222Who starred in the 1959 epic film Ben Hur where in Paris?',
        answers: [
            'Charlton Heston',
            'Clark Gable',
            'Errol Flynn',
            'Lee Marvin'
        ],
        correct: '2'
    },
    {
        qNo: '14_',
        question:
            '133333333333The Eiffel Tower is located where in Paris where in Paris?',
        answers: [
            'de Boulogne',
            'Champ de Mars',
            'Jardin des Plantes',
            'Parc de Belleville'
        ],
        correct: '1'
    },
    {
        qNo: '15_',
        question:
            '1555555555Which Appollo mission landed the first humans on the Mooon ?',
        answers: ['Apollo 7', 'Apollo 9', 'Apollo 11', 'Apollo 13'],
        correct: '1'
    }
];
